<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Puzzle Books Publishing on Book Review System</title>
    <link>https://book-review-system.info/categories/puzzle-books-publishing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Puzzle Books Publishing on Book Review System</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://book-review-system.info/categories/puzzle-books-publishing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Money Selling Sudoku Puzzle Books on Amazon KDP</title>
      <link>https://book-review-system.info/posts/how-to-sell-puzzle-books-on-amazon-kdp-and-make-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://book-review-system.info/posts/how-to-sell-puzzle-books-on-amazon-kdp-and-make-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;full-2025-guide-to-successfully-sudoku-puzzles-books&#34;&gt;Full 2025 Guide to Successfully Sudoku Puzzles Books&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to earn money on Amazon KDP, but very few niches offer the stability, longevity, and predictable earnings that puzzle books do. While many beginners chase journals, notebooks, and coloring books, seasoned publishers quietly build durable incomes with Sudoku, Word Search, Crosswords, Mazes, Cryptograms, and mixed activity books that sell year-round. I’ve spent more than a decade analyzing puzzle niches, helping publishers build catalogs, optimizing listings, and studying buyer behavior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Publish Word Search Puzzle Books on Amazon KDP</title>
      <link>https://book-review-system.info/posts/how-to-publish-word-search-books-on-amazon-kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://book-review-system.info/posts/how-to-publish-word-search-books-on-amazon-kdp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-ultimate-2025-guide-to-word-search-puzzles&#34;&gt;The Ultimate 2025 Guide to Word Search Puzzles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Among all puzzle niches on Amazon KDP, Word Search books stand out as one of the most profitable, beginner-friendly, and evergreen. While many new publishers chase planners, gratitude journals, or coloring books—formats that rise and collapse with trends—Word Search books quietly bring in steady royalties year-round. They appeal to kids, adults, seniors, teachers, travelers, and hobbyists. They are used for entertainment, cognitive training, ESL classes, therapy, and gifts. This creates a unique combination of consistent demand and extremely wide audience reach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
